ANGELO CARDONA

34 Arlington Street • Westbury, NY. 11590 (973) 479 1687

https://github.com/leangele - angelocardona85@gmail.com http://angelocardona.us

SUMMARY

Very experienced in teamwork, with great ability to analyze and solve problems, passion for good practices and design patterns, work with agile methodologies, with skills for learning and teaching, with more than 6 year of experience in web development technologies based in .net (ASP.NET, MVC, ASPNET CORE, WEB API, EF, SQL Server), and work with javascript and some of his frameworks (Jquery, Angular, Knockout), Certified Scrum Master.

EXPERIENCE

INTERSOFT Long Island, NY

February 2017 – Present

System Developer

• Portal Migration: Our team is migrating a software from VB6 to VB.NET 2015 with WPF to be used multiplatform, actually this project i in 50% completed but when finished it will be more fast, better UX and better technologies. **Technology used**: C#,VB.NET, WEB API, WCF, WPF.

DDS LABORATORY, Long Island, NY

August 2016 – February 2017

System Developer

• Lab Track Project: Created real time solution with a dashboard in order to allow the dental laboratory to monitor employee production.

Technology used: Windows Form, Entity Framework, JavaScript, Azure.

ADN SOFTWARE, Medellin, Colombia

February 2015-February 2016

Senior Developer

Caza Talentos Ligna Project: Created ranking system to determine which young athletes would be the best fit for the
teams. Areas tested (psychological, physical, anthropometry, progress). Software was joined with OMS nutritional
report.

Technology used: MVC, ASP.NET, JavaScript, Entity Framework, Web Api, Azure.

CORZATECH. LTDA, Medellín, Colombia

February 2014-February 2015

Lead Developer & SM

• Syscort mob Project: Created application to control the plant production for windows mobile using barcode reader. **Technology used**: Azure, Windows Mobile, ADO.NET, WEF, VISUAL.NET.

ENLACE OPERATIVO, Medellín, Colombia

November 2010-Marzo 2014

Software Engineer

• Light Client Project: Created application saving the client the need and expense of having to buy multiple user licenses

Technology used: ASP.NET, JavaScript, ADO.NET, REST API.

• Notify Agent Project: Created agent to allow clients to receive constant notifications in regards to application errors, etc. sending about 12,000 messages per month.

Technology used: ASP.NET, JavaScript, ADO NET, WCF, SOAP.

Asterix Service Desk Integration Project: an important part of the company is save times between each call, for that they need a way to reduce time between the client call and is create a case, for that was create a integration when the client call they provide his number of identification and pre-create a case he just need add information provide verbally by the client, as a result i Allowed for company to save 45 seconds per call intake.

Technology used: JavaScript, Entity Framework, REST API.

EDUCATION

System Technology - Politecnico JIC Colombia (3 years)

SCRUM MASTER ACCREDITED CERTIFICATION

open certificate - Scrum Institute

www.scrum-institute.org - Register 37377133711241

SKILLS

Bilingual and Fluent in English and Spanish, que mas????